Who is like You Lord in all the earth
Matchless love and beauty endless worth
Nothing in this world can satisfy
Jesus You're a cup that won't run dry
Your presence is Heaven to me
Who is like You Lord in all the earth
Matchless love and beauty endless worth
Nothing in this world can satisfy
Jesus You're the cup that won't run dry
Your presence is Heaven to me
Oh Jesus oh Jesus
All my days on earth I will await
The moment that I see You face to face
Nothing in this world can satisfy
Jesus You're the cup that won't run dry
Your presence is Heaven to me
Oh Jesus oh Jesus
Hallelujah!
You may be seated - thank you.
Hallelujah.
Wow, what a wonderful atmosphere.
I am blessed.
What an awesome atmosphere.
Hallelujah.
BE ALL GOD HAS CALLED YOU
Tell your neighbour, "be all God has called you."
I cannot hear you.
Be all God has called you.
If you want to be all God has called you to be,
you've got to spend time with Him and learn from Him at His feet.
And learn at what?
At His feet.
The main thing about Christianity is not what we do.
You spend all your time on fasting and prayer - fine
You preach everyday in three, four churches. They send you from one place to another - it is good - fine.
You pay your tithe - fine.
You sleep in the church - fine.
All this - fine.
It is not what we do but the relationship we maintain
and the atmosphere produced by that relationship.
If you say you have a relationship with God,
that relationship must definitely produce an atmosphere.
What we do for God is only a reflection of the relationship we have with Him.
What we do for God is only a reflection of the relationship we have with God.
Ask your neighbour, "what are you doing with God?"
I can't hear you.
What are you doing with God?
what are you doing for God?
what are you doing with God?
What you do for God is only a reflection of the relationship you have with Him.
What I am doing is only a reflection of the relationship I have with Him.
What are you doing with God?
What are you doing for God?
Let's hear the song.
Who is like You Lord in all the earth
Matchless love and beauty endless worth
Nothing in this world can satisfy
Jesus You're the cup that won't run dry
Your presence is Heaven to me
Oh Jesus oh Jesus
You listen to that?
To have the presence of God, you must have a great relationship.
A great relationship brings about great works.
What we believe today is: "I am working for God". That is our language.
Instead of saying: "I am working for myself", we say: "I am working for God".
"I am an evangelist", "I am a Christian", "I am working for God", "I am a deacon, deaconess", pastor, bishop.
"I am an usher", "I am a Christ's worker"
Some say they're in the church for God.
And it is because he has nothing else to do out there.
If there was anything to do out there, they would not be here today.
If you receive a very serious phone call
that somebody is ready to pay you billion dollars
you would just walk out of this place.
Just a phone call.
"Hello, they are ready to pay you that billion dollars."
OK, hold on.
Usher, please - where is the restroom here?
He says he is going to the toilet.
But he is not going to the toilet.
He would now enter the toilet and say, "Hello, I can't hear you clearly.
What are you saying?"
He heard him clear, but that language is our friend.
"They are ready to sign the cheque now. Where are you?"
I am very close. Whereas he is not close.
He is not close. He is very far.
He says he is very close because he wants to delay them.
OK, don't worry.
He just walks out - he is going.
Where is he going?
The prayer of T.B. Joshua has been answered.
If my prayer is answered, would you leave me inside the church?
"I will come back and give the testimony."
"We will build the church on the another side"
"This church is too warm - we need more air-condition - I can buy central AC"
What we do for God is only a reflection of the
relationship we have with Him.
Tell your neighbour.
What we do for God is only a reflection of the relationship we have with Him.
I can't hear you.
What you do for God you claim you do for God or do with him or whatever way. I am an Evangelist, I am this, I am that, I am a prayer warrior , I am an intercessor. You donate to charity , help the needy, you help the widow you give trillion dollars to support the work
all these are a reflection of the relationship you have with Him.
Let's go to our Bible.
Romans 8:27 NKJV
"Now He who searches the hearts knows what the mind of the Spirit is."
What does this mean?
This means that the Holy Spirit has a mind.
When you say "a road" - it means there are many roads,
but when you say "the road" - it means its the only.
"Now He who searches the hearts knows what the mind of the Spirit is."
The Holy Spirit has a mind.
We have the mind of Christ.
We have what?
I can't hear you.
We have the mind of Christ, that is, the mind of God.
The mind of Christ is an independent mind.
Satan hates an independent mind.
The mind that will think for itself.
That is, the mind that is determined to find out from God the truth.
He is a good listener but he will listen to you ...he will still find out
from God before taking action.
Satan would want you to take all you hear without question.
Satan wants to take what?
Before you came here you know the way you see this ministry before coming here
you say I must go there to see by myself.
Coming here you see differently.
If you have an independent mind, a mind that will think for itself,
a mind that is determined to find out from God the truth,
you would not have said all sort of things.
"Over my dead body. I would never step in this place"
But today you are here.
... because we are ready to take all, without finding out...
Don't be afraid to say, "I do not know," if you don’t know.
If you know, say, "I know". That is the mind of Christ.
Are you there?
A person has the power to decide.
"Where am I going? Where would I go; here or here...?"
That is, exercising the will through the mind.
Exercising what?
The will through what?
The mind.
"Which direction should I take? I will go there."
The Holy Spirit has the power of choice.
The Holy Spirit has the power of what?
Of choice.
But you - the power you have... to decide.
Decide now.
I will take this one, or let me take this one.
But the Holy Spirit has the power of choice.
How do we know who is speaking?
When a pastor...
Because that name, sometimes may be a title.. or divine
If I come out and say, "I am a pastor", "I am a prophet", "I am a bishop", and I begin to talk,
how do we know who is talking?
The Holy Spirit has a mind.
This means there is also another mind one can talk through.
This shows also that there is another mind.
One can stand to say, "Jesus is Lord" but it is not the voice of the Holy Spirit.
"Jesus is Lord" and it is the voice of the Holy Spirit.
How do we know the one that is the voice of the Holy Spirit
and the one that is not the voice of the Holy Spirit?
Be healed in Jesus' name!
It will sound the same.
Even the one that is not of Holy Spirit will sound better than the one that is of the Holy Spirit.
When you hear it fluently, smoothly.
Uuh my God on the outside very smooth...
But how do we know the voice of Holy Spirit, in these two;
"Be healed in Jesus' name!"
the end we will know.
If the person is healed - this is the voice of Holy Spirit.
"Be healed in Jesus' name!"
If the person is not healed, out of his unbelief
This can be said out of what?...unbelief.
And this means that a person is talking.
A person has the power to decide.
"I will go this way. I will say this. I will not say this. I will do this. I will not do this."
The Holy Spirit has the power of choice.
Take note of these two words.
A person has the power of speech.
S P E E C H.
The Holy Spirit speaks.
Open the book of Acts 8.
Let's look at what happened here
Acts 8:29 NKJV
"Then the Spirit said to Philip, 'Go near and overtake the chariot'."
We all know chariots.
Acts 8:30 NKJV "So Philip ran to him, and heard him reading the prophet Isaiah,
and said, 'Do you understand what you are reading?'"
This means
a person has the power of speech.
The Holy Spirit speaks as He wills.
We have the mind of God, the mind of Christ,
an independent mind.
Satan hates an independent mind,
the mind that will think for itself.
"What are you saying? - You say this, OK."
Ok like what I am saying now you listen to me
If you have an independent mind, you listen to me you will now examine all what I have said
What are you examining it for?
You want to know whether a person that is talking or a prophet that is talking.
There are two persons; a person and a prophet.
You need to examine all this.
Look at what they saying.
The Spirit said.The Christian Community it seems we are all hung
On the last day, if a change does not come,
to many Jesus will say, "I don't know you".
If a change is not coming to the Christian community...
A change must come.
Holy Spirit must intercede now,
because it is getting worse.
What is getting worse?
Many of us are serving God we do not know.
Do you know what I mean by "serving God that we do not know"?
God - you cannot hear from Him, and He cannot hear from you.
We believe so much in what we do with God and do for God, but we never knew that it is merely a reflection
of the relationship we have with Him.
The Spirit of Father must come now and intercede before it is too late.
And it is getting too late now in Christian community.
What do I mean by "getting too late"?
Many are serving God they do not know.
We believe that when you pray God heal me and you are healed, that is the answer
There is another, greater answer, that is better than that.
The best answer is for you to hear from God.
When you begin to hear from Him, you'll begin to know God's opinion
about yourself and about others.
Look at what we are reading here.
A person has the power of speech.
The Holy Spirit speaks as He wills.
A person has the power to decide.
"Where am I going. I will pray later at 6 o'clock I will pray.
because of the nightmare let me go and pray.
Because of the attack I am having,let me open my Bible and put it under the pillow.
That is a decision, you decided not Holy Spirit this time
You open your Bible, place it on your chest and sleep with it, because they are attacking you every day.
You decide when to pray.
40 days, 40 nights is coming - you know the time and when it will be It's in the calendar.
What we do with God is only a reflection of the relationship we have with Him.
A person has the ability to preach, to teach; in Jesus' name. Amen.
We have the ability to do it.
Will through the mind.
The Holy Spirit teaches, preaches, counsels, witnesses, testifies as He wills.
So, the song...
What a wonderful song.
Give it once again
I bless the singer and I bless the composer.
Who is like You Lord in all the earth
Matchless love and beauty endless love
Nothing in this world can satisfy
Jesus You're the cup that won't run dry
Your presence in Heaven to me
Oh Jesus oh Jesus
The presence of God comes by relationship with Him.
The beginning of our message...
The main thing about the Christianity
is not what we do.
Tell your neighbour, "the main thing about Christianity is not what we do,
I dont know what you do you say you are a pastor, evangelist, christian you are this or that just mention it
It is not what we do, but the relationship we maintain.
Your presence is heaven to me
If the presence is Heaven to me, we are talking about the atmosphere.
It means the atmosphere produced by that relationship is Heaven to you.
You say, "Your presence is Heaven to me"
They talk of Heaven to you, the presence.
You are talking about the atmosphere.
Under what atmosphere?
that is the atmosphere produced by that relationship is Heaven.
Go and work on your relationship.
And stop deceiving yourself by saying; "I am a pastor, I am this, I am that".
and wasting your time sleeping in the church.
It's wasting of effort.
Let us work on our relationship.
Tell your neighbour, "work on your relationship".
And stop deceiving yourself saying;
"I am a Christian. I am a Pastor, I am a Prophet, I am a Bishop, I am an Evangelist,
I am a Counselor, I am a Deacon, I am a Deaconess".
Go and work on your relationship.
Yes, because all these titles cannot take us to heaven.
I am a Prophet.
On the last day the Lord will not say, "T.B. Joshua - prophet he is prophet -allow him to enter".
Which kind of a Prophet?
It is relationship.... relationship that will take you to Heaven.
Relationship with Him will take you to heaven.
All this; I am a Pastor, I am a Prophet, I am Deacon, I am a Deaconess, I am a Christian, I am this, I am that...
are symbolic.
Jesus - the hope of Glory.
Tell your neighbour, "work on your relationship"
Work on your relationship.
The atmosphere produced by that relationship will usher you to Jesus.
People hide under these names;
Christianity, hide under I am a prophet, hide under I am a bishop, I am deacon; deaconess, I am this and that
We keep hiding under that name, because this is what people want to hear.
People want to hear; "I am a Bishop", "I am a Prophet", "I am this, that",
"I am a Christian", "I am born-again".
They hide under these names.
Tell your neighbour once again.
The main thing about Christianity
is not what we do
but the relationship we maintain.
The atmosphere produced by that relationship will usher you to Jesus.
We have to work... - this is fundamental.
Don't let anybody to give you any title or name. Work. Your work will give you that name. Leave the title open.
God bless you
Hallelujah.